This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger into the Pirates.
Lucky D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum-gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
Now this is sight!
I can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will come a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
After being separated from his crew, Luffy set out to rescue his captured brother Ace.
To do so, he snuck into the government prison, impelled down.
Now at level four, the burning heat held.
Warden Magellan has ambushed him.
And one final thing.
I will find out exactly how you broke into my prison.
You will spill every last juicy detail to me.
I'll die before I say a word!
Don't do it!
You can't!
Why did you...
Don't get in my way!
Didn't you hear me?
You can't fight him!
Listen, if you touch that poison anywhere,
it'll be the last thing you do!
Down the Venom Road.
Try as you might.
You won't escape from me!
Warden Magellan guards the most dangerous criminals
in the most infamous prison in the entire world.
He's the Lord and Master of Hell itself!
You're not going to let Strawboy face him all alone, are you?
Forgive me!
I tried to warn you, but you wouldn't listen!
Running is the only answer!
I'm sorry, Strawboy!
I'm a coward!
Forgive me!
I suggest you put an end to this nonsense and submit.
And I'm not going to let you execute him!
You hear me?
I'm not getting anywhere.
I can't win without touching you.
I'll make a sacrifice!
You can take my arms, but I won't lose!
You don't...
Ah!
Shit-masuka!
The showdown has come!
Luffy's desperate last attack!
Morons!
What's wrong with you two?
If you had just slipped away when I told you to, I could have blamed this mess on the warden.
We're at the staircase to level three.
There was a raid by two of the escapees.
We've got some casualties here.
Yes, that's right.
We have Buggy the Clown and Mr. Three in custody.
You wanted to go through the gate.
I said fine, but you wouldn't believe me!
Ruin my plan!
Oh!
Ow!
He's a hell of a lot stronger than he looks!
Ah!
Damn hanyable!
I don't wanna be tortured, if that's what's in store for me.
I'm gonna bite off my tongue!
I'm serious!
Here I go!
I'm gonna do it!
I'm really gonna do it!
Ahhhhh!
Ahhhhhhhh!
Oh, my God.
Oh, he's coming!
Get out of my way!
I said move it, you fools!
If you don't want to get hurt, then move! Let me through!
Mr. Two is about to attack!
Get him!
I'm not pulling your tail!
You asked for it!
Drunken Swamp Swamp!
There's no way we can beat Magellan.
I'm not going to dream an impossible dream.
If I'd remain there any longer, I'm 200% sure he would have killed me.
Don't look back!
Just keep running!
The only thing I can do is run!
Come here and run!
Straw Boy!
O not off to rock!
It would seem you have brought me to my knees, boy.
Even a cornered rabbit will fight with teeth and claws.
But now, your hands and arms are covered in my poison.
That's enough to affect your entire body.
You're feeling the pain. I know you are.
Give up already.
Now, come, come!
Quentin Pekka!
Venom!
Glowfish!
See you like this!
Gomp Gomp!
Vendron!
Set pistol!
Not even a scratch!
Fuck!
Venom Cloud!
It's no use. That poison fog is a part of me.
It lives and breathes.
Ha, ha, ha.
Vision getting blurry.
Are your ears ringing?
Gum gum!
Moon!
I said it's no use. Why can't you see that?
There's no escape. You have already been condemned.
Your hands have become useless, haven't they?
In time, my poison will take everything from you.
It doesn't look like your natural
I'm going to bite my tongue off and none of you can stop!
I just can't do it!
Damn it all!
Take them away.
Sir!
What a waste.
Please! Stop it! Have mercy!
No, man!
Torture stinks!
It stinks like ass!
Yeah! Like that!
Hold it right there, chumps!
Hey, who's that?
I know that voice.
He's here.
Now, swan!
Out of ass!
Ah!
Hey! Just who are you?
That guy!
It's Mr. Two!
That man's the other escapee!
I've had enough!
Take this and this and this and this and this and this and this and...
I admit you're quick on your feet, but I think you'll find I'm quite persistent.
What?
Hey, big boy.
Aren't you a cutie?
What are you doing way over there?
What are you doing?
You just don't know when to quit.
Rescuing your brother really means that much to you?
What?
Ah!
The sooner you stop this nonsense, the sooner I end your suffering.
You gum gum pistol!
Hey, jailer. Want to do a condemned man a favor?
Tell me, is something happening on the upper levels?
No, not a thing.
This is pointless, hopeless. You have no right.
Your brother is a notorious criminal who will face his execution in rightful ways.
You are an intruder who has waged open war on the world government.
You've wronged this world, and you must pay.
The law demands Asa's death in Marineford, and so it shall have it.
Do not mistake your misguided attempt at rescuing him for justice.
The law demands Asa's death in Marineford.
That's enough!
Luffy, please.
Stay away.
That's enough!
Luffy, please.
It's not worth it.
You've wronged this world.
You've wronged this world, and you must pay.
The law demands Asa's death in Marineford, and so it shall have it.
That's enough!
Do not mistake your misguided attempt at rescuing him for justice.
Luffy, please.
Stay away.
It's not worth it.
Oh, this is sad to watch.
Now come, come!
Stop!
Are you finally done?
No! Second gear!
Hydra!
Yuck!
My lord, my brother!
Consider this your punishment, child.
There's no way to neutralize the amount of poison your body has absorbed.
You will suffer an agonizing pain for 24 hours, and then you will die.
This is true hell!
Ace...
After losing to Magellan, Luffy is imprisoned on level five.
Even though he knows the warden's poison has no cure,
Bon Clay rushes to his friend's aid, betting on a distant hope.
However, before he can reach him, a pack of army wolves blocks his advance.
On the next, One Piece, for his friend, Bon Clay's deadly rescue attempt, I'm gonna be king of the pirates!
The End